

MEDIA EXECUTIVE with extensive experience creating and writing multimedia proposals for corporate companies, leveraging exemplary interpersonal communication skills to establish and maintain powerful client relations, and adhering to budget and time schedules to strategize and execute company events and promotions. Dedicated team player utilizing media acumen to create and produce audience-centric targeted advertising and programming content in alignment with client objectives. Reliable liaison with keen instinct to support clientele by communicating cross-departmentally to fulfill company projects.

AREAS OF EXPERTISE

- ✓ Performance Marketing
- ✓ Client relationships
- ✓ Communication Skills
- ✓ Ad Sales & Marketing
- ✓ Media Planning
- ✓ Account Management
- ✓ Content/Proposal Writing
- ✓ Event Planning
- ✓ Project Management

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE & ACCOMPLISHMENTS

Major Rocket LLC

Director of Marketing

Oct 2021-Dec 2022

- Oversaw Major Rocket's network of brand and distribution partners, driving sales and customer acquisition through a strategic performance marketing model
- Negotiated and managed over \$2B in partner sales annually, with a focus on building and maintaining strong client relations
- Developed and monitored KPI's for large brand partners including Walmart, Verizon and ADT by leveraging relationships with 40 digital marketing distribution partners to develop powerful strategic partnerships
- Responsible for creative content/ asset management for many large-scale and sustainable marketing campaigns

Viacom CBS Inc. | Smithsonian Channel - New York. NY

Nov 2016-Oct 2021

Ad Sales Media Planner

- Built and revised linear media plans in Wide Orbit Network that met client requirements and company goals
- · Assisted with pricing and analyzing CPMs and revenue trends for both upfront and scatter plans
- Coordinated with Sales Operations, IT, Research, Inventory and Forecasting regarding deal maintenance and optimization
- · Worked with Director of Pricing to generate opportunities for incremental growth
- Worked with marketing to ensure proper distribution of sponsorship elements

Viacom CBS Inc. | BET Networks - New York, NY

Ad Sales & Business Development Manager

2004 - 2007

- Managed on-site promotions and events, utilizing interpersonal communication skills to cross-functionally coordinate company events by collaborating with the company financial department, marketing team, and vendors to enhance product sales.
- Supervised company projects, communicating between clientele and various departments to complete and accomplish
 project goals before deadline by providing the necessary tools, offering inside knowledge, and ensuring workflow
 cohesivity.
- Functioned as liaison for buyers, serving as an internal agent to conduct personal media buys and implement cross-platform marketing to achieve sales goals while relaying information with the financial department to maintain and abide by the set budget.

Previous Experience: Matrix Essentials - Assistant Marketing Manager • Asia Fit '98 - Sales & Marketing Coordinator

EDUCATION
TECHNICAL SKILLS
LANGUAGES

Bachelor of Arts (BA), Economics & French: Smith College

Microsoft Office Suite | Broadway Software | Wide Orbit | Pipe Drive

Fluency: French | Tamil | Hindi